const queries = [
    {
        question: "What is the feature used by the Greeks to support parts of a large slab without the use of a wall?",
        answer: "Column",
        alternates: [
            "Architrave",
            "Abacus",
            "Intrados"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the feature that joins at the top of the temple to help distribute weight?",
        answer: "Capital",
        alternates: [
            "Pedimont",
            "Column",
            "Sima"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the scrolls at the top of Ionian style columns?",
        answer: "Volutes",
        alternates: [
            "Prostyle",
            "Cella",
            "Scroll"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the decorative relief sculpture which lies horizontally near the top of the structure?",
        answer: "Frieze",
        alternates: [
            "Dentils",
            "Cavea",
            "Aedicule"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "An ornament that is placed at the apex of the pediment in the classical style is called?",
        answer: "Acroterion",
        alternates: [
            "Capital",
            "Pilaster",
            "Conch"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Also called a plinth, what is this flat base that supports a pillar?",
        answer: "Pedestal",
        alternates: [
            "Pedimont",
            "Pronaos",
            "Metope"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The style with a double row of columns on all sides, such as The Parthenon, is called?",
        answer: "Dipteral",
        alternates: [
            "Decastyle",
            "Dodecastyle",
            "Amphiprostyle"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Like the Temple at Delphi, what is the name of a circular temple?",
        answer: "Tholos",
        alternates: [
            "Opisthodomos",
            "Propylon",
            "Stylobate"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the cornice, usually at the top of the entablature, meant to trap?",
        answer: "Water",
        alternates: [
            "Dirt",
            "Light",
            "Souls"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name for a sculpted female statue used to support the entablature?",
        answer: "Caryatid",
        alternates: [
            "Atlantide",
            "Entasis",
            "Crepidoma"
        ]
    }
];